{
    "id": "20c26b5d337745a7b0427954700bcac0",
    "title": "During And While",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I read a lot of books …………………. the summer vacation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3f1326f5200947a0a58dc51e34a4d8a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I learned some Spanish ………………… I was working in Spain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5f659df90ce0491cae2553b0d5382bd3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He arrived ………………… I was out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f0c58c7fa7a24b6f962679126090d166"
        },
        {
            "question": "She called me ………………… the lunch break.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "af430002df434d47b174c2fc1c7c569c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was in hospital ……………….. the winter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4d234a109a1649b7b6ef2ea548a86511"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will see you for a few minutes ………………. the afternoon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "69ea3c0188af4a1c93cd7f5359f3143c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I woke up several times ………………… the night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bc6457d8d4d3434288095dfb0f0b4aad"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will phone you ……………… the meeting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b5afb360fe7b45e390f67ae8fa599979"
        },
        {
            "question": "I met him ………………. my stay in Canada.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "150cdc8363d84e0ca30646448152d26a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I met him …………………. I was working in Canada.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "while",
                "during"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1c7c97426f604d8394c92bfc7a173f19"
        }
    ]
}